global.honda 2019-04-17

# Honda Global | privacy-policy

### Honda Website Privacy Policy

Honda is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Honda Website Privacy Policy (this “ Privacy Policy ”) tells you how Honda Motor Co., Ltd (“ **Honda** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”), as the data controller, processes your personal data when you visit, download, or contact Honda in relation to, the Honda Global Website (https://global.honda/, the “ Website ”) that refer to this Privacy Policy (all " **Website** ").

This Privacy Policy also describes your personal data protection rights, including a right to object to some of the processing that Honda carries out. More information about your rights, and how to exercise them, is set out in the “Your Choices and Rights” section.

**_What Personal Data We Collect_**

We process the following types of personal data:

  * **Contact information** : such as your name, address, phone, email and other similar information.
  * **Technical details of your visit to the Website** : such as your IP address, cookie and operating system, browser type (for visits to our Website), details of the device you are using (e.g. your device serial number, unique identification number, MAC address) and technical and event based data in relation to your usage of your device (e.g. internet and Bluetooth pairing and connectivity data and session duration. For further information, see our  [Cookie Policy](https://global.honda/cookie-policy.html).
  * **Any other information you submit to us** : such as opinions and any other information you provide.

**_Why We Collect, Use and Store this Personal Data_**

We collect, use and store your personal data for the reasons set out below.

  * **Where you have given consent.**
  * **Where necessary for Honda’s legitimate interests, as listed below, and where our interests are not overridden by your data protection rights.**

  * to deliver the Website and related services to you;
  * to administer the Website resources;
  * to allow us to improve and optimise the Website and Honda products and services;
  * to respond to your request or enquiry; to contact you for the above purpose; to ask you to provide your opinion or participate in surveys about our vehicles, products and services;
  * to understand which parts of the Website are popular/most used, or those which need changing/upgrading; and
  * to respond to user questions and complaints; and for internal record keeping

  * **Where necessary to comply with a legal obligation.**
  * **Where necessary to protect Honda’s legitimate interests and legal rights, and where our interests and not overridden by your data protection rights.**  
Protecting our legitimate business interests and legal rights. This includes, but is not limited to, use in connection with compliance, regulatory, auditing, legal claims (including disclosure of such information in connection with legal process or litigation) and other ethics and compliance reporting requirements.

Honda will also convert personal data into anonymous data and use it (normally on an aggregated statistical basis) for research and analysis to improve the Website, analyse trends and, tailor products. Aggregated personal information does not personally identify you or any other use of the Website.

When providing Honda with personal data of minors, Honda strongly encourages the prior consent of parents / guardians.

**_How We Share Your Personal Data_**

**(a) Transfers to companies providing services under contract**

Your personal data will be shared with companies providing services under contract to Honda, such the companies set out below:

  * Website provider
  * Website service provider IT hosting
  * IT maintenance provider
  * Adobe analytics provided for the Website improvement and optimization professional advisors. For further information, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://global.honda/cookie-policy.html).

_Transfers outside Japan_  
Your personal data that we collect from you may be stored and processed in Japan or in any other country where service providers maintain facilities. Honda will ensure appropriate safeguards as required by applicable law to ensure the integrity and security of your personal data when engaging such service providers.

_Third party apps_  
Where you download a third party app from the Website, your personal data will be transferred to that third party app provider directly as a separate data controller. Honda is not responsible for the processing of your personal data by such app providers. As such, you should take time to read and understand how your personal data will be used by app providers before you download their apps.

**(b) Transfers to other of Honda group entities**

If it is necessary for responding to your request or enquiry, your personal data will be shared with other entities of Honda group (“Honda group” means Honda, subsidiaries of Honda, affiliate companies of Honda, distributors, dealers and repairers authorized by Honda).

_Transfers outside Japan_  
Some of entity of Honda group maintains facility outside of Japan. Only if you agree, your personal data which Honda collects through the contact form in the Website may be stored and processed in the countries other than Japan. Honda will ensure appropriate safeguards as required by applicable law to ensure the integrity and security of your personal data in this case. You can withdraw above consent to such sharing at any time.

**(c) Transfers to other organizations**

  * Transfers to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose your personal data in order to comply with a legal obligation or if we consider this is necessary for us to protect the rights, property or safety of Honda, our customers or others.
  * Transfers to government authorities and/or law enforcement officials if mandated by law or if required for the protection of our legitimate interests in compliance with applicable laws.

(a) Your general Rights and Choices   

  * You have the right to **ask Honda for a copy** of your personal data; to **correct, delete** or **restrict** processing of your personal data; and to **obtain the personal data you provide in a structured, machine readable format**.
  * You can **object to the processing** of your personal data in some circumstances (in particular, where we don’t have to process the data to meet a contractual or other legal requirement).
  * Where we have asked for your consent, you may **withdraw consent** at any time. If you ask to withdraw your consent to Honda processing your data, this will not affect any processing which has already taken place at that time.

These **rights may be limited** , for example if fulfilling your request would reveal personal data about another person, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law or have compelling legitimate interests to keep.

(b)Your Right to Complain to a Supervisory Authority  
You also have the right to complain to a supervisory authority for data protection, where applicable to your personal data under the applicable laws.

We will retain your personal data only f or as long as we need it for Honda's legitimate interest in accordance with applicable law, or perform a service at your request, or to meet a legal requirement. At the end of the retention period, we will take steps to delete your personal data or hold it in a form that no longer identifies you.

**_Links to third party Websites_**

The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks and advertisers. Honda is not responsible for the content of any websites that are linked to its site. When entering a third party site, it is your responsibility to ensure that you read the privacy policy and legal terms & conditions that apply to that site.

The Website uses cookies to store your preferences and settings and to analyse your browsing experience on the Website. Access logs are automatically recorded when you visit web pages on this Website. For further information, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://global.honda/cookie-policy.html).

**_Disclaimers Regarding Use of Personal Data_**

_**Honda will abide by this Privacy Policy to protect your personal data. Due to the nature of the Internet however, Honda cannot ensure the security of data transmitted to the Website or the security while accessing the Website. You are responsible for personal data transmitted to the Website or to Honda.**_

_**Honda is under no condition responsible or liable for the protection or use of personal data collected by third - party web site s regardless of whether they are linked to by the Website.**_

**_Updates to this Privacy Policy_**

Honda may revise the content of this Privacy Policy periodically in order to protect your personal data, due to circumstances such as laws and regulations relating to personal data, developments in Internet technologies, and changes in services provided by Honda. We will update the date at the top of this Privacy Policy accordingly and encourage you to check for changes to this Privacy Policy, which will be available on the Website. On some occasions, we may also actively advise you of specific data handling activities or significant changes to this Privacy Policy, as required by applicable law.

The Website is controlled by Honda Motor Co., Ltd., which is the data controller for personal data collected via the Website and whose registered address is 2-1-1, Minamiaoyama, Minato-ku, Tokyo 107-8556, Japan.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

< June 8, 2018 >
